(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-06T13:30:12.989419",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
本日は IRyS ファーストコンサート
Today, for IRyS's first concert,
HOPE!
HOPE:Beyond the Stars にご来場いただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for attending HOPE: Beyond the Stars.
最後までライブを──！ イェーイ！
Enjoy the live until the very end──! Yay!
えっと、最後までライブを楽しく聞いていただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To help you enjoy the concert to the fullest,
I have a few announcements for you.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画器材の使用を固くお断りしています。
Photography, recording, and videotaping
are strictly prohibited during the performance.
館内は禁煙、禁、禁煙となっております。
The venue is strictly non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。No smoking!
Please refrain from smoking. No smoking!
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, please do not push yourself
and notify nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなにご迷惑になったり講演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Moshing, diving, jumping, throwing objects on stage,
or disrupting the show is strictly prohibited.
当たり前じゃないすか！ はい！
Isn't that obvious! Yes!
ルールは、ルールは
Rules, rules...
守って盛り上がってくださーい！
please follow them and get hyped!
ね？はーい！
Right? Yeah!
っ、演出のご都合上、通路通路に荷物を置いたり足を出したりしないようにしてください。
Please don't leave belongings in the aisles
or stick your legs out for production reasons.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。はい。
Also, cameras will be in the venue,
and audience seats may appear on camera.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
These may be used for promotions,
so please understand this in advance.
そしてみんな、ペンライト持ってきてますかー？
And everyone, did you bring
your light sticks?
ええ、ありがとうございます！
Yay, thank you so much!
今日はね、会場内にこの曲はこの色、みたいなペンライトカラーのイメージが左右のサービススクリーンとステージにあるモニターの一部に表示されます。
Today, light stick colors for each song
will be shown on screens and monitors.
助かるよね！はい。
That helps, right? Yeah.
ええと、みんなそれに合わせてカラーを変更してくれたらうれしいです。
I'd be happy if you could change
your colors to match them.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #IRISConcert2026 です。
Also, the live hashtag is
#IRISConcert2026.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくだサーイ！
Please use the hashtag
to get super hyped!
それでは開演までもう少しです。
Well then, we're almost
at the start of the show.
みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！アイリスでしたー！
Let's all get hyped together!
This was IRIS!
英語いきます。
Now in English.
Thank you so much for joining me today for Iris's, my first concert, Hope Beyond the Stars!
Thank you so much for joining me today
for my first concert, Hope Beyond the Stars!
Before we begin, I have a few things I'd like to let you know so you can enjoy the concert to the fullest.
Before we begin, I have a few things
I'd like to let you know...
Photography and the use of audio or video recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
Photography and recording equipment
are strictly prohibited.
Smoking is not permitted inside the venue, so please refrain from smoking.
Smoking is not permitted inside the venue,
so please refrain from smoking.
If you start feeling unwell, please don't push yourself, please let a staff member nearby know.
If you feel unwell, please don't push yourself
and let a staff member know.
Mosh, stage diving, jumping excessively, throwing things onto the stage, and any other behavior that could disrupt other guests or disrupt the show are strictly prohibited.
Mosh, stage diving, jumping excessively,
and throwing things are prohibited.
Have fun and get hyped while following the rules!
Have fun and get hyped
while following the rules!
For production and safety reasons, please make sure not to leave any belongings in the aisles or stick your legs out into them, please.
Please do not leave belongings in the aisles
or stick your legs out.
In addition, cameras for video streaming and photography will be operating inside the venue, so you may appear in the footage or photos, these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes, so please keep that in mind, thank you very much for your understanding.
Cameras will be operating inside the venue,
so you may appear in footage or photos.
And, everyone, did you all bring your light sticks? Yes, second time, yeah!
And everyone, did you all
bring your light sticks?
During the concert, we'll be displaying the light stick color for each song on the side screens and some of the monitors on stage, it's going to show up like, you know, one song is like red so it should show up as red, yeah, I'd love it if you could change your light stick colors to match them, please, and thank you.
We'll be displaying light stick colors
for each song on screens.
And don't forget that the official hashtag for the concert is #IRISConcert2026, be sure to use it and help spread the excitement!
And don't forget the official hashtag
is #IRISConcert2026!
We're almost ready to get started, let's get excited and enjoy the concert together! IRISでしたー!
Let's enjoy the concert together!
This was IRIS!
願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
それは、あなた。
It would be you.
そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
I will gift you with
奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
Hope made of miracles.
さあ、希望への旅をはじめよう
Our journey towards Hope begins
夢で見たような風景に似てた
Similar to the scenery I saw in a dream,
こんなに賑やかな世界は
this bustling world is
something i wanted to know; why were they smiling so?
it’s so easy to see now that i found the key
they might clap their hands, sing a song
dancing to express the way they feel
and i feel something start to come over me
i feel i wanna join with you
join with you and share more joy with you, joy with you
i really want to know my own true happiness
i feel i wanna join with you join with you
and share more joy with everyone
my heart won't stop racing
Baby, how's your life? Are you living free?
Let's forget everything and have some fun
Chu, chu, chu
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice
Baby, baby there's no need to think twice, dari-wari-woah
Make it your night, make it your fight, make it your spotlight
Get out from the hamster wheel and rule your life
Five, four, three, two, one, play dice
So the space went "bang" and we were all born
The order we knew, ripped and torn
But we have no time to complain
'Cause life is short, can't do it over again
If we can laugh, it doesn't matter where or when
Be 自チュ奔放
Physics don't play the dice? So let trouble stir and rise
Be limits, bounds, rules or chains, 意味なんてもん あ あ あ ああい
So we don't give a chu, やなことはそっと mute
So find something new, 身体中一瞬で夢中 ha
No cage can trap this rat
Now here I will recite to you
The only thing that will hold true
YOLO is my ninja way
It's time put those moves out there on display
Why stress about tomorrow, when you've got today?
Be 余チュ縷々
今が最高か最悪かなんて誰も知らない
人生 鼠生チュ生ってまじでみすぼ あ あ ああい
Wow, aren't we sick as chu?
我々ってエグい cute
So rush on to our route, 花火走らせまるで見電流 ha
No math can settle this rat
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice
Baby, baby there's no need to think twice, dari-wari-woah
Make it your night, make it your fight, make it your spotlight
Get out from the hamster wheel and rule your life
Five, four, three, two, one, play dice
Fire inside, burn it like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Call your lover, be my player
Keep me burning, while your lover calls my name
Please, love, burn me away
Blaze on fire,
Make me a believer, I'm getting dizzy
from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burn it like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Call your lover, be my player
Keep me burning, while your lover calls my name
Please, love, burn me away
Blaze on fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burn it like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Call your lover, be my player
Keep me burning, while your lover calls my name
Please, love, burn me away
Blaze on fire!
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice
here we just play dice (Yeah)
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
I'm only getting harder
Show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you to burn it for me
Blaze on fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burn it like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Call your lover, be my player
Keep me burning, while your lover calls my name
Please, love, burn me away
Blaze on fire, make me a believer
I'm getting dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burn it like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare
Call your lover, be my player
Keep me burning, while your lover calls my name
Please, love, burn me away
Blaze on fire!
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
High
Stakes
Dreams
Out, lost, free
逃げ出そうぜ
さぁ、まだまだ壊していくよ
S-G-C-H-O-O-L
Let's escalate!
Find another playground
Shadows of my regret
And I couldn't forget the words ringing in my head
Say you'd touch a rat if you say so again
I'm headed toward the fire
My head is stuck in overdrive
Homeward, do straight into what they all said
I can do! Ready to burn the tires
This is my design, get set outside
Go hit it again
Don't hover the break, do what it takes
Till they don't know your name
Steering your soul right towards your fate
Cuz it's all yours to take, so ready up
No, don't hesitate, you'll waste your life
There's just no time to wait, you'll never break
And it's no mistake that you've got this far
Look you be afraid, really mean escalate
Lagging behind the rest
I made it be excused for running just on fumes
I dreamed I could be the best
I'll make it all suit you
Just wait and I'll soon tune
You'll reverse all the cruise control
Forgot about the rhythm, sounds
Oh, I'm red-lining and driving at 80 mph
Got no need to turn the car
Just skip the mighty spark
Go head, step on the gas, don't stop
Go hit the gas, don't hover the brakes
Do what it takes, till they know your name
To bring yourself right towards the fate
Crashing into it, cause this all used to take
Already up, no, don't contemplate
You'll waste your life, there's just no time to wait
You'll never break, and it's no mistake
That you've got this far, won't you be afraid
Lagging behind the rest
I made it be excused for running just on fumes
I dreamed I could be the best
I'll make it all suit you
Just wait and I'll soon tune
You'll reverse all the cruise control
Forgot about the rhythm, sounds
Oh, I'm red-lining and driving at 80 mph
Got no need to turn the car
Just skip the mighty spark
Go head, step on the gas, don't stop
Above the limit, feel my heart rising
Drifting away, I'm flying far
My engine's burning
Hotter than fire, self-pushing more
Exalting all for myself
And I'm young, go hit the gas, don't hover
Go hit the gas, don't hover the brakes
Do what it takes, till they know your name
To bring yourself right towards the fate
Crashing into it, cause this all used to take
Already up, no, don't contemplate
You'll waste your life, there's just no time to wait
You'll never break, and it's no mistake
That you've got this far, won't you be afraid
Hit the highway
Believing and as the way
Believing in us today
Hey, going my way, I'll get you where you need to be
Ready? Let's hit the road
You looked a little lonely, I caught you getting deep in despair
Why don't you call me, you know I'm gonna answer your prayer
Turn up the ignition, I'll pay you for a spin
We don't wanna know where we're going
You want a bask in heaven's glow, then son
Look out below
Count the sky cause I'm a star
They call me like a jawbreaker
But I can be more, I gotta be more
I don't want a floor, I'm energetic
I can be the girl of your dreams
It's up to burn, I'm a goddess, aren't you saved?
So baby, my baby, treat me like a lady
Optic cure for your blues
Oh baby, my baby, you're the one I choose
Let me be your muse
It's up to burn, I'm a goddess, aren't you saved?
So baby, my baby, treat me like a lady
Optic cure for your blues
Oh baby, my baby, you're the one I choose
Let me be your muse
It's up to burn, I'm a goddess, aren't you saved?
So baby, my baby, you're the one I choose
Let me be your muse
All I'm looking for
Now you know all about me, bet you can't live without me
So come on and get me, babe, and let me show you my speed
Chasing me like the devil, hit the pedal to the metal, follow me
A heavenly body in a TV smile
Don't leave me waiting, do you want to know my style?
'Cause I can be an angel or a demon, I'll get you dreaming
It's up to burn, I'm a goddess, aren't you saved?
So baby, my baby, treat me like a lady
Optic cure for your blues
Oh baby, my baby, you're the one I choose
Let me be your muse
休日最高のリミックスを届けていくバンドメンバーを紹介するよ
Kyuujitsu wa saikou no remix wo todokete iku band member no shoukai suru yo
まずはベース！
Mazu wa bass!
I watched you bleed,
I can be the girl of your dream,
Hit lock button, hit pause, hit stop and let's leave,
I got nothin' to sorry, I'm okay,
So baby, baby, this dream be like a laser,
On the joy for your blues,
So baby, baby, you're the one I choose,
Let me be your muse, let me be your muse now,
I watched you bleed,
I can be the girl of your dream,
Hit lock button, hit pause, hit stop and let's leave,
So baby, baby, this dream be like a laser,
On the joy for your blues,
So baby, baby, you're the one I choose,
Let me be your muse, let me be your muse now.
Hi! IRyS, it's IRyS!
Hi! It's IRyS!
From HOPE, promise!
From Project HOPE!
Thank you so much for coming!
Thank you so much for being here today,
to my very first solo live concert!
初めてのソロライブ、HOPE Beyond the Starsに来てくださりありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to my first solo live, HOPE Beyond the Stars!
いやー、いよいよ始まっちゃった！
Man, it's finally started!
いや始まった、やばい、なんかずっとこのライブに向けて準備してきたけど、
Man, it started! Oh man, I've been preparing for this live for so long,
待って何の意味、何を私今やってるの？
wait, what do you mean, what am I even doing right now?
いや「私今」って言ってるのがもう信じられないんですけど、いや本当に、ありがとうございます。嬉しいです！
I can't believe I'm saying "right now," but really, thank you so much. I'm so happy!
いや初めての、あの夢にまで見たね、ファーストライブ！
For my very first, um, dream-come-true first live!
夢は奇跡じゃない、みんなで起こす魔法をテーマに、
With the theme that dreams aren't miracles, but magic we create together,
みんなに叶えてもらったこのライブを最高にする魔法をかけたいと思っています！
I want to cast a spell to make this live you helped me achieve the best!
I am going to cast a spell on all of you today. It's a magical night, that's the theme of this live.
Yay! I can see all of you.
みんな見えてるよー！
I can see all of you guys!
うわあ、やばい、すごくいっぱい人いる！みんな、いっぱい人いる...！
Wow, oh man, there are so many people! Everyone, there are so many people...!
ええとね、ほんとにね、披露したい楽曲がね、もうとにかくね、ありすぎて、
Um, really, you know, there are just too many songs I want to perform,
全部詰めこんだら、とにかく凄いセットリストの...
and if I crammed them all in, the setlist became...
曲数になっちゃいました！はい！
It became a huge number of songs! Yes!
ええと、みんな最後まで楽しんでついてきてくれると嬉しいです！
Um, I'd be so happy if you all enjoy it and follow me to the end!
あの、I have a lot of original songs and I tried to fit as many as I can and from that it's a pretty long setlist. Yeah!
Um, I have a lot of original songs and I tried to fit as many as I can, and from that, it's a pretty long setlist. Yeah!
So, you know, you guys might get tired maybe, but I hope you guys, you know, keep the energy up until the very end,
and it could turn out like everyone got tired midway, but...
and you might feel like you got tired midway, but...
ありがとう！ね、今日は会場、会場...
Thank you! And, you know, today the venue, the venue...
ね、この曲はこの、そう、あのこの曲はこのって、さっき、あのあいの...
You know, this song is this color, wait, this song is this color—earlier, um, I...
見ましたよね？ 見ました？
Did you see it? Did you see?
ちぎがえし、じいかえし…… prompt change to this color on the monitors?
Changed... prompt changed to this color on the monitors?
イェーイ！ Are you guys following it?
Yeah! Are you guys following it?
みんな、言うこと聞いてます？
Everyone, are you listening to what I say?
あのプロンプトの。聞いてくれたら嬉しいな。
That prompt. I'd be happy if you listened.
もちろんね、あの、反抗したい気持ちもまあね、少なはあるのはわかるんですけど。
Of course, you know, I understand there's a bit of rebellious feeling too.
えー、そう言うね、この曲は、この色ってみたようなね、ペンライトカラーのイメージが左右のサービスモニターの
Uh, so, this song, this color, you know, penlight color images on the left and right service monitors
ステージモニターの一部に表示されてます。今回ちょっと新しいあの、チャレンジだと思います。ホールでは。
is displayed on a part of the stage monitors. I think this is a bit of a new challenge this time in the hall.
So this is the first time I think we're trying out, um, using pen light colors on the sides, like, you know, showing, oh, what pen light color for what song on all the monitors.
So if you're curious, and you don't know what color should I turn on, then you follow the monitor, it says the color.
イェーイ！
Yay!
ばっちりだよね！
Spot on!
ばっちりだよ！イェーイ！
Spot on! Yeah!
よかった！ えーっとね。
Great! Um...
ちなみに、私のファーストアルバム、「DARLING S」みんな聞いてくれた？
By the way, did everyone listen to my first album, "DARLING S"?
イェーイ！ よかった！
Yay! Great!
I'm glad you guys listened to my first album that came out just a bit like a video a few months ago.
えー、ね、今回はね、あの、そちらのアルバムからもちろん、たくさんの中楽曲をね、今日披露しようかなと思ってます。
Um, right, this time, of course, from that album, I'm thinking of showcasing many songs today.
I'm going to showcase a lot of songs from that album. Of course, I will also still be showcasing a lot of songs from past EPs and what not too, obviously.
Yes, and of course, those EPs and single songs, I'm also picking up songs, so please look forward to that.
えーっと、はい！
Um, yes!
ちなみにね、今回はね、ユーロビートからバラードまで、いろんなジャンルをね、あの、披露しようかなと思ってます。
By the way, today, from Eurobeat to ballads, I'm thinking of showcasing various genres.
I'm going to have, of course, the Eurobeat songs, which you know you guys heard some of it already, and some ballad, more, you know, soft songs in the setlist as well.
So please enjoy the variety. あの、しかも今日は生バンドでお届けしてます！
So please enjoy the variety. And what's more, today we are delivering it with a live band!
イェーイ！ やあ、もう本当にありがたい！ありがたいし、もう光栄です！
Yay! Wow, I'm truly grateful! Grateful and so honored!
ありがとうございます！ Thank you so much for band members. It still feels surreal to be able to perform with a live band, oh my goodness.
Thank you so much! Thank you so much to the band members. It still feels surreal to be able to perform with a live band, oh my goodness.
ありがとうございます！ ええと、リハの時からね、もうとにかく興奮が止まらなくて、
Thank you so much! Um, ever since rehearsals, my excitement just wouldn't stop,
はやくみんなにお届けしたかったんです。
and I wanted to deliver it to everyone quickly.
I've been wanting to perform for you guys with this live band for ages, I'm really glad I'm finally able to do it. Yay!
そう、I hope you guys enjoy this till the very end. そしてね、ええと、この
So, I hope you guys enjoy this till the very end. And um, this
え、今回のね、ライブですが、ええ、ライブの感想、是非ハッシュタグ
concert today, um, concert impressions, please use hashtag
まあ、ここにハッシュタグあるか、多分ないだろうな、今回は。
Well, is there a hashtag here? Probably not this time.
ハッシュタグね、あの「IRIS Concert 2026年」でたくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです。みんなで盛り上げましょう！
Please post a lot with the hashtag "IRIS Concert 2026". Let's hype it up everyone!
Please use the hashtag for watching this live, use the #IRISConcert2026, post it on Instagram, let's all hype it up. Yeah!
ありがとうございます！ イェーイ！ そして
Thank you! Yay! And
I think you guys probably noticed by probably, you know, そろそろそのタイミングだよねっていう。
I think you guys probably noticed by probably, you know, it's about that timing, right?
ええと、そして、まだ言ってないよ。
Um, and, I haven't said it yet.
ええと、YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方は、このMCパートで終了です！
Um, for those watching on YouTube or TikTok, this MC part is the end!
イェーイ！ イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
えって、えって言ってですと、まあでもみんな会場にいるから関係ないよね。
Eh? saying "eh?", well, everyone's in the venue so it doesn't matter right?
でも、あの、配信のね、みんな、配信のみんなー、I can see you guys.
But, um, everyone watching the stream, stream everyone, I can see you guys.
Yeah, free part ending, yes! It's ending after this.
あ、まだまだね、一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄から配信、配信のチケットのリンクがあるんで、踏んで買ってね！ Yeah!
Ah, for those who still want to get hyped together, there's a link to the stream tickets in the description box, so click and buy it! Yeah!
Um, by, uh, yeah, free part is ending, but if you guys are interested, if you guys want to see the rest of this concert, you can get the streaming ticket from the link in the description of what you're watching, whether it's YouTube or TikTok.
Yeah! Boy! Yeah! Boy!
はい、ぜひ買ってね。はい、ええと、みんな、あと
Yes, please definitely buy it. Yes, um, everyone, also
今回は、ええと、ステージ固定カメラ、そう、言い忘れた。
this time, um, stage fixed camera, right, I forgot to say.
ええと、ステージ固定カメラも、ついて、あの、ついてるんじゃなくて、追加でね、追加料金で変えます。すごいよね！
Um, stage fixed camera also, not attached, but additionally, you can change it for an additional fee. Amazing right!
Yeah! There's also  a staged fixed camera view of the concert for streaming tickets, you can add it as an add-on to your regular streaming ticket. Yeah, isn't that nice? That means you get to see  everything like me. Yeah! The whole time ずっと
Yeah! There's also a staged fixed camera view of the concert for streaming tickets, you can add it as an add-on to your regular streaming ticket. Yeah, isn't that nice? That means you get to see everything like me. Yeah! The whole time, the entire time!
リス… IRISの動き全部見れますよ、それで。
Listeners... You can see all of IRyS's movements, you know.
すごいよね。はい。
Pretty amazing, right? Yeah.
なのでぜひ、あのね、結構おトクな、あの、なんていうの、
So please, you know, it's a pretty great value, um,
追加のコンテンツなのでぜひご検討よろしくお願いします。
additional content, so please consider checking it out.
さて、まだまだライブは始まったばっかりですからね。
Now then, the live is still just getting started.
さっそく次の曲、ちょっとその前に水飲んでいいですか。
For our next song... but before that, can I drink some water?
頑張れありがとう。Thank you. はい。
Ganbare, thank you! Thank you. Yep.
じゃ、次の曲。
Now, for the next song.
えっと、すごく、あの、爽やかな、爽やかっていうか、もうしっとり、しっとり目のバラード行きたいと思ってます。
Um, I want to go with a really, um, refreshing—well, not refreshing, but a mellow, mellow kind of ballad.
すごく私にとって大事な曲で、It's going to be a ballad song, that is really important, that is really important to be, please listen to,
It's a really important song to me, it's going to be a ballad song that is really important, that is really important to be, please listen to,
心臓が止まるまでぜひ聞いてください。
please listen to it until your heart stops beating.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!